https://www.ncobs.org/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
North Carolina Outward Bound School is committed to protecting your online privacy.
The following discloses our online information gathering and dissemination practices. By using the site and entering information about yourself, you agree to be legally bound by this privacy policy, as amended from time to time. If this policy is not acceptable and you are unwilling to be bound by it, please do not enter any information about yourself through this site.
Our overall policy is extremely simple: If we collect information from you, we use it only for the purposes for which it was collected, and the other limited purposes outlined below.
Here are the details of our privacy policies. This statement may change over time -- please review it periodically. By using this web site after we post any changes to this Privacy Policy, you agree to accept those changes. If at any time you choose not to accept the terms of this Privacy Policy, then you will not enter information about yourself; if you have already done so, then you may opt-out as explained below.
Types of Information Collected
NCOBS collects two types of user information. We collect some non-personally identifiable information automatically and some from our registration forms and online surveys. Non-personally identifiable information might include your IP address, your browser type or operating system, the domain name from which you linked to our site, your zip code, your age, and other general demographic information. We use this non-personally identifiable information to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our website; and we may share it with our affiliates, or with our other business partners on an aggregated basis.
Our site's donations, registration and contact forms, online surveys, and merchandise transactions may also request or require users to give us personally identifiable information (like their name, telephone number, home address and e-mail address). We may use the information from our donations form, registration form, merchandise purchase forms and surveys to contact the user, but users may opt-out of receiving future mailings. We will not sell or disclose your personally identifiable data to any third party unless: (i) we change website hosts or our host transfers business assets (as further described below); (ii) we first obtain permission from you; (iii) we need to share it with agents or contractors who perform services for us; or (iv) we are required by law to disclose it.
If you provide contact information, staff from NCOBS may inquire to clarify your comment or question, or to learn about your level of customer satisfaction with our services.
Cookies
We may use "cookies" to determine whether you have visited our site previously and to save and remember any preferences that you set while using our site. Cookies also allow us to measure activity on our site and to improve your user experience, for example by remembering your passwords and viewing preferences, thus allowing you to visit any member-only parts of the site without re-registering. Our cookies cannot retrieve any other data from a hard drive or obtain an e-mail address. Although a user has the ability to modify most browsers to either accept all cookies, notify the user when a cookie is sent, or reject all cookies, it may not be possible to utilize certain services if cookies are rejected.
Links
This site contains links to other sites. The NCOBS site is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. We encourage you to review the privacy policy and any other online policies or agreements of any sites to which you link.
Security
We will take reasonable steps to ensure the safety of your personally identifiable information. This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. However, we do not assume any liability for third-party usage of your personal information, whether obtained legally or illegally from our system.
Children
The NCOBS site does not seek to collect any information from children under the age of 13. If any child provides us with personally identifiable information, a parent or guardian may notify us and such information will be deleted from our records.
Correct/Update
This site gives users the opportunity to change and modify information previously provided information by sending us an email through our contact form.
Contacting the Website
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, you can send a message through our contact page.
USE OF THIS SITE SIGNIFIES YOUR AGREEMENT TO THE TERMS OF USE AND PRIVACY POLICY.
Sign Up for Updates
Stay informed on North Carolina news and updates! Please fill out the form
below to begin receiving our email newsletter.
888.756.2627
Email us
2582 Riceville Road,
Asheville, NC 28805
©ALL CONTENT 2020 NORTH CAROLINA OUTWARD BOUND SCHOOL
NAVIGATION
Course Finder
Privacy Policy
About
FAQs
Programs
Blog
PART OF THE NATIONAL NETWORK OF OUTWARD BOUND SCHOOLS IN THE U.S.
North Carolina Outward Bound School is a registered 501(c)(3). Contributions are therefore tax-deductible to the full extent provided by the law. Financial information about North Carolina Outward Bound School is available from the NC State Solicitation Licensing Branch at (919) 733-4150.
